Guide to the Firebrand Books records, 1984-2000.
Firebrand Books records,
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Firebrand Books records, 1984-2000
7670
Firebrand Books (Ithaca, N.Y.).
58 cubic ft.
Manuscripts, financial records, personnel records, computer files, ephemera.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Complete archives of Firebrand Books, founded by Nancy Bereano and recognized by the Lambda Literary Awards with their Publisher’s Service Award in 1996. Includes detailed files on published books; rejection letters; invoices; distributors' reports; vendor files; files on conferences and events the publisher attended, including her 1991 service on the Advisory Committee to the Human Sexuality Collection; mailing list; lists of Firebrand employees and interns; summary of financial donations to Firebrand; Firebrand's web site; and posters that decorated the office.
ORGANIZATIONAL HISTORY
From 1984 to 2000, Firebrand Books published exceptional literary fiction, nonfiction, and poetry on lesbian and feminist themes. Publisher Nancy Bereano won the Publisher's Service Award at the "Lammy" or Lambda Literary Awards in 1996. She took the first risk on author Dorothy Allison, publishing the double-Lammy winning Trash in 1988. (It won awards in the categories of Lesbian Fiction and Small Press). Keeping more than 80 titles in print, including the entire "Dykes to Watch Out For" series, poetry by Audre Lorde, Minnie Bruce Pratt, and Cheryl Clarke, and short stories, novels, and nonfiction from the likes of Ruthann Robson, Lesléa Newman, Mab Segrest, Leslie Feinberg and Judith Katz, (and more than a few Lammy winners and finalists), Bereano was at the forefront of lesbian and small press publishing for 16 years.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Files on each book published, including author and reviewer correspondence, print history and promotional material; rejection letters; invoices; distributors' reports; vendor files; files on conferences and events the publisher attended; file from publisher's service on the Advisory Committee to the Human Sexuality Collection, 1991; Firebrand's mailing list of organizations (ca. 1450); lists of Firebrand employees and interns and summary of financial donations to Firebrand; a zip disk containing Firebrand's web site; and posters that decorated the office.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Firebrand Books (Ithaca, N.Y.).; Alden, Joan, Before our eyes: a novel.; Healy, Eloise Klein, Artemis in Echo Park.; LaFavor, Carole, 1948-, Along the Journey River: a mystery.; Bereano, Nancy, 1942-
Subjects:
Lesbians' writings--Publishing.; Feminist fiction--Publishing.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
SERIES LIST
Series I. Author/Book Files
Boxes 1-32
Series II. Manuscript Rejections
Boxes 33-43
Series III. Financial Records
Boxes 44-63
Series IV. Conferences and Related Activities
Boxes 64-65
Series V. Administrative Information and Posters
Box 65 and Map Case
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Author/Book Files
  - Along the Journey River: Pending, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Along the Journey River: Contracts, 1995-2000 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Along the Journey River: (British Edition) A Renee LaRoche Mystery, by Carole laFavor, The Women's Press Ltd. 1996, 1997. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Along the Journey River: CD Audio Recording-Calliope Women's Chorus "Promise of Spring", 1995 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Along the Journey River: General, 1997-2000 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Along the Journey River: General, 1994-1996 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Along the Journey River: Promo Materials, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Along the Journey River: A Mystery by Carole laFavor, Firebrand Books 1996 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Along the Journey River: Reviews, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Along the Journey River: Review Copies, 1996-2000 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Artemis in Echo Park: Pending, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Artemis in Echo Park: Contracts, 1989-2000 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Artemis in Echo Park: General, 1995-2001 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Artemis in Echo Park: General, 1991-1994 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Artemis In Echo Park: General, 1982-1990 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Artemis in Echo Park: Promo Materials, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Artemis in Echo Park: Poetry by Eloise Klein Healy, Firebrand Books 1991 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Artemis in Echo Park: Reviews, 1991-1998 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Artemis in Echo Park: Review Copies, 1991-1999 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Before Our Eyes: Pending, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Before Our Eyes: Contracts, 1992-2000 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Before Our Eyes: General, 1993-2000 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Before Our Eyes: Promo Materials, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Before Our Eyes: A Novel by Joan Alden, Firebrand Books 1993 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Before Our Eyes: Reviews, 1993-1995 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Before Our Eyes: Review Copies, 1993-1997 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Beneath My Heart: Pending, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Beneath My Heart: Contracts, 1989-2000 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Beneath My Heart: General, 1997-2000 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Beneath My Heart: General, 1992-1996 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Beneath My Heart: General, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Beneath My Heart: General, 1985-1989 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Beneath My Heart: Promo Materials, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Beneath My Heart: Poetry by Janice Gould, Firebrand Books 1990 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Beneath My Heart: Reviews, 1990-1995 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Beneath My Heart: Review Copies, 1990-1997 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - The Big Mama Stories: Pending, 1989-1998 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - The Big Mama Stories: Contracts, 1987-2000 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - The Big Mama Stories: (German Edition) by Shay Youngblood, Atlantik 1989, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - The Big Mama Stories: General, 1998-2000 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - The Big Mama Stories: General, 1992-1997 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - The Big Mama Stories: General, 1989-1991 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - The Big Mama Stories: General, 1986-1988 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - The Big Mama Stories: Promo Materials, n.d (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - The Big Mama Stories: by Shay Younblood, Firebrand Books 1989 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - The Bi Mama Stories: Reviews, 1989-1997 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - The Big Mama Stories: Review Copies, 1989-2000 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - The Black Back-ups: Pending, 1992-1995 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - The Black Back-ups: Contracts, 1992-2000 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - The Black Back-ups: General, 1997-2000 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - The Black Back-ups: General, 1994-1996 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - The Black Back-ups: General, 1990-1993 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - The Black Back-ups: General, 1984-1989 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - The Black Back-ups: Promo Materials, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - The Black Back-ups: Poetry by Kate Rushin, Firebrand Books 1993 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - The Black Back-ups: Reviews, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - The Black Back-ups: Review Copies, 1992-1999 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Bleeding Out: Pending, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Bleeding Out: Contracts, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Bleeding Out: General, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Bleeding Out: Promo Materials, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Bleeding Out: A Mystery by Baxter Clare, Firebrand Books 2000 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Bleeding Out: Reviews, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Bleeding Out: Review Copies, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Breathless: Pending, 1995-2000 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Breathless: Contracts, 1995-2000 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Breathless: General, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Breathless: General, 1996-1999 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Breathless: General, 1988-1995 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Breathless: Promo Materials, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Breathless: Erotica by Kitty Tsui, Firebrand Books 1996 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Breathless: Reviews, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Breathless: Review Copies, 1995-2000 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Bruised Fruit: Pending, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Bruised Fruit: Contracts, 1998-2000 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Bruised Fruit: General, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Bruised Fruit: General, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Bruised Fruit: Promo Materials, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Bruised Fruit: A Novel by Anna Livia, Firebrand Books, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Bruised Fruit: Reviews, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Bruised Fruit: Review Copies, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - A Burst of Light: Pending, 1988-1995 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - A Burst of Light: Contracts, 1987-2000 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - A Burst of Light: Essays by Audre Lorde, Women's Press 1988 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - A Burst of Light: General, 1998-2000 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - A Burst of Light: General, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - A Burst of Light: General, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - A Burst of Light: General, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - A Burst of Light: General, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - A Burst of Light: General, 1989-1990 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - A Burst of Light: General, 1986-1988 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - A Burst of Light: Promo Materials, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - A Burst of Light: Essays by Audre Lorde, Firebrand Books 1988 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - A Burst of Light: Reviews, 1988-2000 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - A Burst of Light: Review Copies, 1988-2000 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Cecile: Pending, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Cecile: Contracts, 1989-2000 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Cecile: General, 1993-2000 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Cecile: General, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Cecile: General, 1989-1990 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Cecile: Promo Materials, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Cecile: Stories by Ruthann Robson, Firebrand Books 1991 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Cecile: Reviews, 1991-1993 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Cecile: Review Copies, 1991-2000 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Cookin' With Honey: Pending, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Cookin' With Honey: Contracts, 1995-2000 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Cookin' With Honey: General, 1996-2000 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Cookin' With Honey: General, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Cookin' With Honey: Promo Materials, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Cookin' With Honey: What Literary Lesbians Eat, by Amy Scholder, ed., Firebrand Books 1996 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Cookin' With Honey: Reviews, 1996-1999 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Cookin' With Honey: Review Copies, 1996-2000 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Crime Against Nature: Pending, 1990-1991 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Crime Against Nature: Contracts, 1989-2000 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Crime Against Nature: General, 1999-2000 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Crime Against Nature: General, 1996-1998 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Crime Against Nature: General, 1993-1995 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Crime Against Nature: General, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Crime Against Nature: General, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Crime Against Nature: General, 1986-1989 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Crime Against Nature: Promo Materials, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Crime Against Nature: Poetry by Minnie Bruce Pratt, Firebrand Books 1990 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Crime Against Nature: Reviews, 1990-1993 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Crime Against Nature: Review Copies, 1990-2000 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - A Crystal Diary: Pending, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - A Crystal Diary: Contracts, 1996-2000 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - A Crystal Diary: General, 1998-2000 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - A Crystal Diary: General, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - A Crystal Diary: General, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - A Crystal Diary: Promo Materials, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - A Crystal Diary: A Novel by Frankie Hucklenbroich, Firebrand Books 1997 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - A Crystal Diary: Reviews, 1997-1998 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - A Crystal Diary: Review Copies, 1997-1998 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Diamonds Are a Dyke's Best Friend: Pending, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Diamonds Are a Dyke's Best Friend: Contracts, 1986-2000 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Diamonds Are a Dyke's Best Friend: General, 1993-2000 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Diamonds Are a Dyke's Best Friend: General, 1988-1992 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Diamonds Are a Dyke's Best Friend: General, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Diamonds Are a Dyke's Best Friend: Promo Materials (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Diamonds Are a Dyke's Best Friend: Reflections by Yvonne Zipter, Firebrand Books 1988 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Diamonds Are a Dyke's Best Friend: Reviews, 1988-2000 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Diamonds Are a Dyke's Best Friend: Review Copies, 1988-1997 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Don't Explain: Pending, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Don't Explain: Contracts, 1997-2000 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Don't Explain: General, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Don't Explain: General, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Don't Explain: General, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Don't Explain: General, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Don't Explain: Promo Materials, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Don't Explain: Short Fiction by Jewelle Gomez, Firebrand Books 1998 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Don't Explain: Reviews, 1998-1999 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Don't Explain: Review Copies, 1998-2000 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Dykes to Watch Out For: Pending, 1986-1999 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Dykes to Watch Out For: Contracts, 1985-2000 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Dykes to Watch Out For: v. 1 by Alison Bechdel, Quality Paperback Book Club 1997 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Dykes to Watch Out For: General, 1999-2000 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Dykes to Watch Out For: General, 1995-1998 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Dykes to Watch Out For: General, 1991-1994 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Dykes to Watch Out For: General, 1987-1990 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Dykes to Watch Out For: General, 1984-1986 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Dykes to Watch Out For: Promo Materials, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Dykes to Watch Out For: Cartoons by Alison Bechdel, Firebrand Books 1986 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Dykes to Watch Out For: Reviews, 1986-1991 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Dykes to Watch Out For: Review Copies, 1986-1999 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Dykes to Watch Out For-The Sequel: Pending, 1992-2000 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Dykes to Watch Out For-The Sequel: Contracts, 1990-2000 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Lepakko elamaa (Dykes to Watch Out For-Finnish): by Alison Bechdel, Kaantopiiri 2000 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Lesbiennes a Suivre (Dykes to Watch Out For-French): by Alison Bechdel, Prune Janvier 1994 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Dykes to Watch Out For-The Sequel: General, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Dykes to Watch Out For-The Sequel: General, 1997-1999 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Dykes to Watch Out For-The Sequel: General, 1994-1996 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Dykes to Watch Out For-The Sequel: General, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Dykes to Watch Out For-The Sequel: General, 1990-1991 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Dykes to Watch Out For-The Sequel: Promo Materials, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Dykes to Watch Out For-The Sequel: by Alison Bechdel, Firebrand Books 1992 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Dykes to Watch Out For-The Sequel: Reviews, 1992-1997 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Dykes to Watch Out For-The Sequel: Review Copies, 1992-1999 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Dykes to Watch Out For-1990 Calendar: Contracts, 1988-1990 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Dykes to Watch Out For-1990 Calendar: General, 1988-1991 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Dykes to Watch Out For-1990 Calendar: Promo Materials (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Dykes to Watch Out For-1990 Calendar: Reviews, 1989-1990 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Dykes to Watch Out For-1991 Calendar: Contracts, 1990-1991 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Dykes to Watch Out For-1991 Calendar: General, 1990-1998 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - DTWOF 1991 Calendar: Promo Materials (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - DTWOF 1991 Calendar: Reviews, 1990-1991 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - DTWOF 1991 Calendar: Review Copies, 1990-1991 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - DTWOF 1992 Calendar: Contracts, 1990-1992 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - DTWOF 1992 Calendar: General, 1990-1993 (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - DTWOF 1992 Calendar: Promo Materials (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - DTWOF 1992 Calendar: Reviews, 1991 (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - DTWOF 1992 Calendar: Review Copies, 1991 (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - DTWOF 1993 Calendar: Contracts, 1991-1993 (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - DTWOF 1993 Calendar: General, 1991-1993 (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - DTWOF 1993 Calendar: Promo Materials (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - DTWOF 1993 Calendar: Review Copies, 1992-1993 (Box 66, Folder 12)
  - DTWOF 1994 Calendar: Contracts, 1992-1994 (Box 66, Folder 13)
  - DTWOF 1994 Calendar: General, 1992-1998 (Box 66, Folder 14)
  - DTWOF 1994 Calendar: Promo Materials (Box 66, Folder 15)
  - DTWOF 1994 Calendar: Reviews (Box 66, Folder 16)
  - DTWOF 1994 Calendar: Review Copies, 1993-1994 (Box 66, Folder 17)
  - DTWOF 1995 Calendar: Contracts, 1993-1995 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - DTWOF 1995 Calendar: General, 1993-1997 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - DTWOF 1995 Calendar: Promo Materials (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - DTWOF 1995 Calendar: Reviews, 1994 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - DTWOF 1995 Calendar: Review Copies, 1994-1995 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - DTWOF 1996 Calendar: Contracts, 1994-1996 (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - DTWOF 1996 Calendar: General, 1994-1998 (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - DTWOF 1996 Calendar: Promo Materials (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - DTWOF 1996 Calendar: Review Copies, 1995-1996 (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - DTWOF 1997 Calendar: Contracts, 1995-1997 (Box 67, Folder 10)
  - DTWOF 1997 Calendar: General, 1995-1998 (Box 67, Folder 11)
  - DTWOF 1997 Calendar: Promo Materials (Box 67, Folder 12)
  - DTWOF 1997 Calendar: Reviews, 1996-1997 (Box 67, Folder 13)
  - DTWOF 1997 Calendar: Review Copies, 1996 (Box 67, Folder 14)
  - Eight Bullets: Contracts, 1994-2000 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Eight Bullets: General, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Eight Bullets: General, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Eight Bullets: General, 1996-1999 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Eight Bullets: General, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Eight Bullets: General, 1988-1994 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Eight Bullets: Promo Materials, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Eight Bullets: tape cassette of "Fresh Air" with Terry Gross, WHYY Philadelphia, n.d.; tr-11672 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Eight Bullets: One Woman's Story of Surviving Anti-Gay Violence by Claudia Brenner, Firebrand Books 1995 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Eight Bullets: Reviews, 1995-1999 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Eight Bullets: Review Copies, 1995-2000 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - The Escape Artist: Pending, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - The Escape Artist: Contracts, 1994-2000 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - The Escape Artist: General, 1998-2000 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - The Escape Artist: General, 1994-1997 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - The Escape Artist: Promo Materials, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - The Escape Artist: A Novel by Judith Katz, Firebrand Books 1997 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - The Escape Artist: Reviews, 1997-2000 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - The Escape Artist: Review Copies, 1997-2000 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Evil Dead Center: Pending, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Evil Dead Center: Contracts, 1996-2000 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Evil Dead Center: (British Edition) by Carole laFavor, Women's Press Ltd. 1998 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Evil Dead Center: General, 1996-2000 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Evil Dead Center: Promo Materials, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Evil Dead Center: A Mystery by Carole laFavor, Firebrand Books 1997 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Evil Dead Center: Reviews, 1996-2000 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Evil Dead Center: Review Copies, 1997-2000 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Exile in the Promised Land: Pending, 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Exile in the Promised Land: Contracts, 1989-2000 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Exile in the Promised Land: (Hebrew Edition) by Marcia Freedman 1990, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Exile in the Promised Land: General, 1993-2000 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Exile in the Promised Land: General, 1991-1992 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Exile in the Promised Land: General, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Exile in the Promised Land: General, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Exile in the Promised Land: Promo Materials (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Exile in the Promised Land: A Memoir by Marcia Freedman, Firebrand Books 1990 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Exile in the Promised Land: Reviews, 1990-1992 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Exile in the Promised Land: Review Copies, 1990-2000 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Experimental Love: Pending, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Experimental Love: Contracts, 1993-2000 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Experimental Love: General, 1997-2000 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Experimental Love: General, 1992-1996 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Experimental Love: Promo Materials, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Experimental Love: Poetry by Cheryl Clarke, Firebrand Books 1993 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Experimental Love: Reviews, 1993-1994 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Experimental Love: Review Copies, 1993-2000 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Eye of a Hurricane: Pending, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Eye of a Hurricane: Contracts, 1987-2000 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Eye of a Hurricane: General, 1990-2000 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Eye of a Hurricane: General, 1987-1989 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Eye of a Hurricane: Promo Materials, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Eye of a Hurricane: Stories by Ruthann Robson, Firebrand Books 1989 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Eye of a Hurricane: Reviews, 1989-2000 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Eye of a Hurricane: Review Copies, 1989-1999 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Falling to Earth: Pending, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Falling to Earth: Contracts, 1998-2000 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Falling to Earth: General, 1999-2000 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Falling to Earth: General, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Falling to Earth: Promo Materials, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Falling to Earth: A Novel by Elizabeth Brownrigg, Firebrand Books 1998 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Falling to Earth: Reviews, 1998-1999 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Falling to Earth: Review Copies, 1998-1999 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - The Fires of Bride: Pending, 1988-1991 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - The Fires of Bride: Contracts, 1986-2000 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - The Fires of Bride: (British Edition) by Ellen Galford, The Women's Press 1986 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - The Fires of Bride: General, 1986-2000 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - The Fires of Bride: Promo Materials, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - The Fires of Bride: A Novel by Ellen Galford, Firebrand Books 1988 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - The Fires of Bride: Reviews, 1987-1997 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - The Fires of Bride: Review Copies, 1988-2000 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Food & Spirits: Pending, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Food & Spirits: Contracts, 1990-2000 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Food & Spirits: (Canadian Edition) by Beth Brant, Press Gang 1991 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Food & Spirits: General, 1998-2000 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Food & Spirits: General, 1993-1997 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Food & Spirits: General, 1991-1992 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Food & Spirits: General, 1988-1990 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Food & Spirits: Promo Materials, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Food & Spirits: Stories by Beth Brant, Firebrand Books 1991 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Food & Spirits: Reviews, 1991-1993 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Food & Spirits: Review Copies, 1991-1999 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Forty-three Septembers: Pending, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Forty-three Septembers: Contracts, 1992-2000 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Forty-three Septembers: General, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Forty-three Septembers: General, 1997-1999 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Forty-three Septembers: General, 1994-1996 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Forty-three Septembers: General, 1990-1993 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Forty-three Septembers: Promo Materials, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Forty-three Septembers: Essays by Jewelle Gomez, Firebrand Books 1993 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Forty-three Septembers: Reviews, 1993-1996 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Forty-three Septembers: Review Copies, 1993-1999 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Free Ride: Pending, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Free Ride: Contracts, 1990-2000 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Free Ride: General, 1989-2000 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Free Ride: Promo Materials, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Free Ride: A Novel by Marilyn Gayle, Firebrand Books 1991 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Free Ride: Reviews, 1991-1994 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Free Ride: Review Copies, 1991-2000 (Box 8, Folder 19)